d4toys.com 2019-06-13

# 

### _Privacy Notice_

D4 Toys Ltd. (owned and operated by the same group as Sentinel International Co., Ltd.) values the users of our website. Your privacy and trust are very important to us. We recognize that you may be concerned about our collection, use, and disclosure of the personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") that we collect when you use the website and the services offered on the website .This Privacy Policy describes the information that we collect from you, how we collect this information, and what we do with it after we collect it. By using the website you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. If you have any questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [_info@d4toys.com_](mailto:info@d4toys.com). This Privacy Policy applies to all users of this website.

### _Conditions of Use information_

**How D4 uses the information you provide?**

If you give us your personal information, we will use this information to register you with our website, to administer our website services, and/or to process any orders you may place online. When you place an order, make a purchase or save your information online, we will use your e-mail and postal address to send you information about our products, services, and promotions and to help us learn more about your shopping preferences but only if you give us your permission. From time to time, we may use this information to contact you via e-mail, postal mail, or telephone to learn more about your shopping preferences. You always have the choice not to receive marketing information or calls. We may contact you, subject to the choices you have made, via e-mail, postal mail, or telephone, to conduct market research and learn more about how we can improve our product offerings. To serve you better, we may combine information you give us and information about your product interest and purchases with information from third parties, including demographic information and information that is publicly available. We may also combine this information with information from our affiliates. We use that combined information to enhance and personalize your shopping experience with us, and to communicate with you in accordance with this policy.

**Does D4 share your information with others?**

D4 does not sell, rent or disclose our client's names, addresses, e-mail addresses or other personal information to any non-affiliated entity. As necessary, your personal information may be processed by these third parties, solely for the purpose of assisting D4 in these endeavors and subject to strict contractual confidentiality obligations. We do not otherwise disclose your information to third parties, unless required by law or in connection with a legal claim or proceeding. In the unlikely event of a sale of some or all of our business, D4 will disclose your personal information to a purchaser that agrees to abide by the terms and conditions of this privacy policy.

**How do I Make Choices about Receiving Promotional Communications?**

D4 would like to communicate with you only if you want to hear from us. If you are registered with us and would like to delete or update your registration and personal details from our database, please inform us [_info@d4toys.com_](mailto:info@d4toys.com) to unsubscribe. If you prefer not to receive promotional information from us or our affiliated brands, or if you do not want us to use your information to enhance your shopping experience, please let us know by writing to us or by sending us an e-mail [info@d4toys.com](http://www.d4toys.com/info@d4toys.com) . Please be sure to include your full name and the e-mail address you used when you registered or made a purchase from us. If you ask us to remove your name and address from promotional lists, we will maintain your name in a "do not contact" file to ensure that we can honor your request. It may take up to 10 working days to process your e-mail request, and 4 to 8 weeks to process your postal mail request, during which period you may continue to receive communications from D4. Please also note that your on-line purchase will be confirmed through e-mail. In addition, we may also need to contact you via phone, e-mail or postal mail with other questions regarding your order.

### Membership information

D4 members can enjoy many privileges, including newsletters, participation in special D4 offers and promotions and streamline shopping. Over time we will be expanding membership benefits to include personalized services on the site and other special benefits. When you join D4, we need to know your name, email and mailing addresses, and we may request that you complete the profile survey in order to allow us to serve you better.

### Ordering information

When you place an order with D4 you will be asked to provide details such as credit card number and shipping address. This allows us to process and fulfill your order and to notify you of your order status.

### Contests and Promotions

We may from time to time organize or host contests and promotions and in doing so ask for information including your name, email and mailing address, telephone number and customer preferences. We'll use this information to notify you if you've won a contest, and to help shape our future contests or promotions.

### Newsletters and Email Promotions

We use email to communicate news and special promotions to our D4 members. If you would rather not receive these messages, you can choose to do cancellation for subscription via [_My Account_](http://www.d4toys.com/index.php?route=account/login).

### How can I change, delete, or update my information?

Most of your account information can be changed in the [_My Account_](http://www.d4toys.com/index.php?route=account/login) section of the D4 website. If you have any questions about what information is stored or would like to obtain a copy of such information, please contact us at _[_info@d4toys.com_](mailto:info@d4toys.com)_ . After receiving proof of your identity, we will provide the information to you, and you may request that we delete or change any or all of the information.

### Your consent

By using our website, you consent to the collection and use of your personal data in a manner consistent with these privacy guidelines. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, so you will always be aware of our policies and practices in relation to personal data.

### Cookies

We use cookies in order to improve your shopping experience when you visit D4. Cookies are small pieces of information that your web browser stores on your computer when you visit a website. Our cookies let us personalize your visits to D4 and recognize you when you return. Information collected from these cookies may be used for the purposes laid out above in this privacy policy.  
Most browsers automatically accept cookies. You can disable cookies on your computer by indicating this in the “preferences” or “options” 「menus」 in your browser. If you disable cookies, you will not be able to shop at D4 but will still be able to visit selected areas of the site.

### Contact Us

If you have any comments or queries regarding our privacy policy, please send an e-mail to [_info@d4toys.com_](mailto:info@d4toys.com)

In the event of a conflict between a translated version of these terms and the English language version, the English language version shall control.
